Guide to the Ralph W. Cummings Papers
Ralph W. Cummings Papers
1840-2001
1840 2001
MC 00312
The Ralph W. Cummings Papers document the personal and professional life of Ralph W. Cummings. The primary focus of the collection is Cummings' career as a professor, researcher and administrator working at North Carolina State University and with international organizations in the fields of soil science and agronomy. The collection also contains the personal papers and letters of Ralph Cummings and the Cummings family papers which include a number of land deeds and legal documents dating from 1840 until 2001 as well as the personal papers of extended family members.
Ralph W. Cummings (1911-2001) was born in Reidsville, North Carolina. He was the head of the Department of Agronomy at North Carolina State University from 1942 until 1947. He held a number of administrative positions for the University over the scope of his career, as well as working in research and leadership positions for a number of national and international organizations concerned with world agriculture and agricultural education and research.
39 linear feet
North Carolina State University Libraries, Special Collections Research Center
Gift of Ralph Cummings Jr. and Eunice Cummings in 2001 (Accn. no. 2001-0015)
The collection is divided into three main series: Personal Papers, Photographs, and Professional Papers.
The Personal Papers are further divided into three subseries: Cummings Family Papers, Ralph W. Cummings Personal Correspondence, and Ralph W. Cummings Personal Documents.
The Professional Papers are further divided into three subseries: Correspondence, Writing, and Research and Related Papers. Some correspondence and writing is found in the Research and Related Papers as well.
Substantial overlap exists in the subjects and persons found in the Personal and Professional series.
Ralph W. Cummings (1911-2001) was born in Reidsville, North Carolina, on 13 December 1911. He was the son of William and Sarah Elizabeth Huffhines Cummings. He graduated from Reidsville High School in 1928 and went on to North Carolina State College of Agriculture and Engineering (later North Carolina State University) where he obtained a Bachelor of Science degree in 1933. He earned a Ph.D. in Soil Science from Ohio State University in 1938.
Cummings worked as an assistant and associate professor at Cornell University in Ithaca, New York, from 1937 until 1942. He joined the faculty at North Carolina State College of Agriculture and Engineering in 1942 as the head of the Agronomy Department, a position he held until 1947. He held positions at North Carolina State College as first Associate Director, then Director, of the North Carolina Agricultural Experimental Station from 1948 until 1954, the head of the North Carolina Agricultural Mission to Peru from 1955 to 1956, the Administrative Dean for Research from 1969 to 1971, and finally, as an Emeritus Professor of Soil Science from 1977 until 1991.
Cummings was professionally involved in agricultural research and development for a number of other academic and private organizations as well. From 1956 until 1957 he was the field director and principal representative of the Rockefeller Foundation in India. From 1963 to 1968, Cummings served as Associate Director for Agricultural Sciences for the Rockefeller Foundation in New York City. He was the Ford Foundation's Agricultural Program Adviser for Asia and the Pacific from 1971 to 1972. He served as the Director of the International Rice Research Institute (IRII) in Manila, Philippines, in 1972; the Director General of the International Crops Research Institute for the Semi Arid Tropics (ICRISAT) in Hyderabad, India, from 1972 until 1977; the Chairman of the Technical Advisory Committee (TAC) for the Consultative Group on International Agricultural Research (CGIAR) from 1977 until 1982, and acting Director General of the International Irrigation Management Institute headquartered in Sri Lanka from 1983 to 1984.
Cummings was the recipient of the Ohio State University Distinguished Service Award in 1970, the Presidential End Hunger Award in 1988, the North Carolina State University Alumni Association Award in 1991, the Soil Science Society of America Distinguished Service Award in 1993,and the North Carolina State Outstanding Alumni Award in 1997. He received Honorary Degrees from Jawaharlal Nehru Agricultural University (Jabalpur, Madhya Pradesh, India) in 1967, North Carolina State University in 1968, Punjab Agricultural University (Ludhiana, Punjab, India) in 1970, the Govind Ballabh Pant University of Agriculture and Technology (Udham Singh Nagar, Uttarakhand, India) in 1971, and Ohio State University in 1992. He was awarded the Watauga Medal by North Carolina State University in 1995. The Cereal Research Lab at the Indian Agricultural Research Institute was renamed Cummings Laboratory in his honor.
Cummings was a member of the American Society of Agronomy, American Academy of Arts and Sciences,and Rotary International. He served as the vice president of the Rotary Club of Raleigh, North Carolina, from 1952 to 1954 and the president from 1953 to 1954.
Cummings married Mary Parrish (1913-1989) of Reidsville, North Carolina, in 1936 and they had four children: Ralph Waldo, Walter B., William K., Mary Ann Hardee. Cummings married Eunice Perkinson in 1993. He died 25 June 2001.
The Ralph W. Cummings Papers document the personal and professional life of Ralph W. Cummings.
The primary focus of the collection is Cummings' career as a professor, researcher and administrator working in the fields of Soil science and agronomy during the course of which he was as a member and director of several international foundations and organizations concerned with agricultural research and the advancement of agricultural education around the globe such as the Ford Foundation, the Rockefeller Foundation and World Bank. Specific areas of research interest were aquaculture, tree crops, plant genetics and agroforestry. Cummings carried out his work in many different locations outside the United States, among them: India, Africa, Peru, the Philippines, Sri Lanka, and Indonesia.
Also included are Cummings family papers which include a number of land deeds and legal documents dating from 1840 until 2001, as well as the personal papers of Cummings' brother, Robert L. Cummings, and Robert Cummings' daughter, Gloria Cummings. These family papers also include correspondence with Gloria Cummings' associate, Francis De Graaff, a professor of Russian who taught at Reed College, Welles College, Black Mountain College, Harvard University, and Bryn Mawr College.
The Photograph series consists primarily of color slides taken during Ralph W. Cummings' professional international travels.
International Council for Research in Agroforestry; International Crops Research Institute for the Semi-arid Tropics; International Irrigation Management Institute; International Laboratory for Research on Animal Diseases; International Livestock Centre for Africa; International Rice Research Institute; Cornell University; International Service for National Agricultural Research; North Carolina State University--Faculty--History; Ohio University; Rockefeller Foundation; Rotary International; Sahel Institute; Soil Science Society of America; West Africa Rice Development Association; World Bank; Rotary Club Raleigh, N.C.; Cummings Ralph W. 1911-2001; Asian Institute for Rural Development Bangalore, India; American Society of Agronomy; Consultative Group On International Agriculture Research; Ford Foundation; Cummings Robert L.; Green Revolution; Research Aquaculture; Research Agroforestry; Research Agronomy; North Carolina Agricultural education; North Carolina Research Agriculture; Agriculture Indonesia; Agriculture India; Agriculture Africa; United States Agriculture; Societies, etc. Agriculture; Agriculture Peru; Agriculture Pakistan; Photographs Peru; Photographs; Photographs Indonesia; Photographs India; Research Tree crops; History Raleigh (N.C.); Research Soil science; Research Plant genetics; Photographs Sri Lanka; Photographs Philippines
- Personal Papers, 1840-2001; 1840 2001; 4 linear feet
  This series contains the personal and legal documents and correspondence of Ralph W. Cummings as well as the extended Cummings family. A significant portion of the family papers were generated by Ralph W Cummings' brother Robert Cummings and his niece Gloria Cummings. Also included are legal papers and land deeds dating into the first half of the 19th century. Cummings' personal correspondence includes letters written to his family as well as friends and work associates. The documents include news clippings related to his work, travel and family. There are some letters in the documents subseries and there is also some overlap between the Personal Papers series and the Professional Papers.
  - Cummings Family Papers, 1840-1995
    - Robert L Cummings letters concerning Gloria Cummings and Frances De Graaff, 1959-1981 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Robert L Cummings letters to Gloria Cummings and Frances De Graaff, 1959-1981 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Gloria Cummings letters to Mrs. J Cortada (maternal grandmother), 1960-1962 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Gloria Cummings report cards, 1947-1954 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Robert Cummings correspondence with Ralph W Cummings, 1937-1941 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Robert Cummings family papers, certificates and photographs, 1907-1966 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Family correspondence concerning estate, 1949-1999 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - William Cummings estate, 1900-1958 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Extended family correspondence, 1947-1990 (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - A. G. and Gladys MacWilliams Estate, 1954-1995 (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - Housekeepers accounts for "mother and father,", 1945-1946 (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - William Cummings (brother), Rockville Centre, New York, 1938-1939 (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - William Cummings (father), Reidsville, North Carolina tax records, 1948-1953 (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - William Cummings (father), Reidsville, North Carolina, estate, 1953-1957 (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - Gladys MacWilliams estate, 1962-1979 (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - "Violets to Greet You" printed book, circa. 1900 (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - William Cummings autograph book, 1988 (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - Unidentified photographs, circa 1890 (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - William Cummings estate, 1900-1954 (Box 73, Folder 1)
    - Deeds and legal papers (1 of 2), 1840-1920 (Flatfile 1)
    - Deeds and legal papers (2 of 2), 1840-1920 (Flatfile 2)
  - Ralph W. Cummings Personal Correspondence, 1940-1998
    - Personal correspondence, 1942-1949 (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - Personal correspondence, 1954-1955 (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence, 1954-1969 (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence - transfer from Peru to India, 1956 (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - Cummings correspondence "vol. II", 1956-1957 (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence, 1960-1984 (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - "RWC Personal", 1960-1966 (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - Family correspondence, 1961-1965 (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - RWC Personal correspondence, 1963-1968 (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence - Transfer from India to NYC, 1965-1966 (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence with University of California at Riverside, 1965-1966 (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - Personal correspondence, 1967-1971 (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - Personal correspondence, 1969 May - December (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - Personal correspondence, 1969 Jan- April (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence, 1969 (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence, 1970 (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence (1 of 2), 1975-1977 (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence (2 of 2), 1975-1977 (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence, 1982-1985 (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence Golden Wedding Anniversary, 1986 (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence Bhyravabhotla Radhakrishna Murty, 1986-1989 (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - 80th Birthday Messages, 1991 (Box 5, Folder 8)
    - Personal correspondence, 1998 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Ralph W. Cummings Personal Documents, 1926-2001
    - Patti Hardee, Fayetteville Academy Work Project, 1986 (Box 5, Folder 10)
    - Family writings William and Ralph Jr, 1966-1969 (Box 5, Folder 11)
    - India with family, 1990 (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - India mementos cards and pictures, 1977 (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - Menus and invitations, 1970-1985 (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - Photographs, 1974 (Box 6, Folder 4)
    - Testimonials, 1991 (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - Mary- favorite quotations, 1950-1989 (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - Friends' obituaries, 1982-1992 (Box 6, Folder 7)
    - Mary P Cummings - death, 1989 (Box 6, Folder 8)
    - Ralph Cummings interview questions and audiotape, 2001 (Box 6, Folder 9)
    - Cummings family clippings, 1950-1980 (Box 6, Folder 10)
    - Ohio State University graduate school admissions, 1933-1953 (Box 6, Folder 11)
    - Certificates and Awards, 1931-1971 (Box 6, Folder 12)
    - NCSU Agronomy outstanding alumni award plaque, 1997 (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - Ohio State Distinguished Service Award Plaque, 1970 (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - Citations, 1938-1970 (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - Letters of departure from Rockefeller Foundation assignment in India, 1966 (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - Clippings (1 of 3), 1938-1980 (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - Clippings (2 of 3), 1938-1980 (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - Clippings (3 of 3), 1938-1980 (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - Sebastian family Father-Son farm agreement, 1954 (Box 8, Folder 2)
    - Jesse Sebastian correspondence from Johnston Youth Center, 1970-1971 (Box 8, Folder 3)
    - Residence 812 Rosemont Ave Raleigh, North Carolina, 1960-1974 (Box 8, Folder 4)
    - Insurance, 1952-1970 (Box 8, Folder 5)
    - Ralph and Eunice Cummings Medical Records (1 of 3), 1998-2000 (Box 8, Folder 6)
    - Ralph and Eunice Cummings Medical Records (2 of 3), 1998-2000 (Box 8, Folder 7)
    - Ralph and Eunice Cummings Medical Records (3 of 3), 1998-2000 (Box 8, Folder 8)
    - Residence 2M 165 West End Avenue New York, NY, 1967-1968 (Box 8, Folder 9)
    - Ralph Cummings Jr "The Future of India's Agriculture and Implications of the Green Revolution" (1 of 3), 1971 (Box 12, Folder 1)
    - Ralph Cummings Jr "The Future of India's Agriculture and Implications of the Green Revolution" (2 of 3), 1971 (Box 12, Folder 2)
    - Ralph Cummings Jr "The Future of India's Agriculture and Implications of the Green Revolution" (3 of 3), 1971 (Box 12, Folder 3)
    - Early clippings, 1940-1969 (Box 12, Folder 4)
    - Menus - Indonesia, 1969-1970 (Box 12, Folder 5)
    - Awards and certificates, 1924-1999 (Box 12, Folder 6)
    - RWC tributes, 1953-1991 (Box 12, Folder 7)
    - Early academic awards, 1928-1938 (Box 12, Folder 8)
    - North Carolina Retired Senior Executives Program, 1982 (Box 12, Folder 9)
    - Residence at 110 The Midway, Ithaca, New York, 1941-1943 (Box 8, Folder 9)
    - Awards and certificates, oversized, 1924-1982 (Flatfile 3)
- Photographs, 1950-1991; 1950 1991; 1.5 linear feet
  The Photographs series consists primarily of color slides taken during Cummings' professional travels. There are images of conferences, crop research, and professional associates as well as landscape, travel portraits, still objects, personal and familial subjects. Also included are black and white prints of Cummings and associates in China.
  - Slides - China, 1979 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Slides - Indonesia, 1969-1970 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Slides - field problems of tropical rice, circa. 1970 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Slides - Rockefeller Foundation Indian Agriculture program slides, 1964-1972 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Unlabeled slides box 1, [196?] (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Unlabeled slides box 2, 1977 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Unlabeled slides box 3, [1956-1977?] (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Loose slides various locations: India, Peru, Indonesia, unknown, crop shots, diagrams, 1954-1977 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Slides - New York, New England, Canada, 1941 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Slides- Jamaica, 1951 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Slides - Europe, [1950-1977?] (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Slides - crops, unidentified locations, [1965-1966 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Slides - Jerusalem, [1956-1977?] (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - India game hunting and wedding slides, 1956-1967 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Slides - Bullfighting, Spain, 1964 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Slides - Peru (1 of 2), 1956 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Slides - Peru (2 of 2), 1956 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Slides - India scenes, Republic Bay, Misc., 1956 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Slides - India wheat (1 of 2), 1956 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Slides - India wheat (2 of 2), 1956 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Slides - family, 1955 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Slides - India, ICRISAT, IIRI, Indonesia, 1956-1972 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Nigeria, Moscow, Peru, Flowers, [1956-1977?] (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - ILCA Slide Set, [1956-1980?] (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Slides - Various International Subjects (1 of 3), [1950-1980?] (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Slides - Various International Subjects (2 of 3), [1950-1980?] (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Slides - Various International Subjects (3 of 3), [1950-1980?] (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Black and White photos from China, [1970s?] (Box 11, Folder 9)
- Professional Papers, 1952-1997; 1952 1997; 33.5 linear feet
  The Professional Papers series comprises the largest part of the collection, with the bulk of the material falling between 1976 and 1982. The Correspondence subseries contains letters concerning various research projects and administrative issues as well as planning for conferences and consortia. Correspondence is organized alphabetically in some cases and chronologically in others. Whenever possible the original order was maintained. Professional Writings contains academic papers, notes, and speeches written by Cummings over the course of his career. The items in the Research and Related Series contain notes, correspondence, writings by Cummings as well as other academic and professional researchers working in the fields of agronomy, soil science, and various other areas of agricultural education. This subseries also contains administrative papers associated with the numerous organizations with which Cummings was affiliated, including the Rockefeller Foundation, the Ford Foundation, the International Rice Research Institute (IRII), the International Crops Research Institute for the Semi Arid Tropics (ICRISAT), the International Irrigation Management Institute, Rotary International, and the Rotary Club of Raleigh, North Carolina.
  - Professional Correspondence, 1970-1990
    - A, 1970-1980 (Box 13, Folder 1)
    - B, 1977-1981 (Box 13, Folder 2)
    - C, 1977-1981 (Box 13, Folder 3)
    - F, 1977-1981 (Box 13, Folder 4)
    - G, 1977-1981 (Box 13, Folder 5)
    - G-I, 1980-1982 (Box 13, Folder 6)
    - H, 1977-1981 (Box 13, Folder 7)
    - I, 1977-1981 (Box 13, Folder 8)
    - J-L, 1980-1982 (Box 14, Folder 1)
    - J-L, 1978-1992 (Box 14, Folder 2)
    - L, 1978-1980 (Box 14, Folder 3)
    - M, 1977-1981 (Box 14, Folder 4)
    - M-N (1 of 2), 1980-1981 (Box 14, Folder 5)
    - M-N (2 of 2), 1980-1981 (Box 14, Folder 6)
    - O, 1977-1981 (Box 14, Folder 7)
    - P, 1977-1981 (Box 14, Folder 8)
    - R, 1977-1981 (Box 14, Folder 8)
    - S (1 of 2), 1977-1982 (Box 15, Folder 1)
    - S (2 of 2), 1977-1982 (Box 15, Folder 2)
    - R-T, 1980-1982 (Box 15, Folder 3)
    - U, 1979-1981 (Box 15, Folder 4)
    - V, 1977-1981 (Box 15, Folder 5)
    - U-W, 1981-1982 (Box 15, Folder 6)
    - W, 1977-1981 (Box 15, Folder 7)
    - X-Z, 1980-1981 (Box 15, Folder 8)
    - Chronological file 1977 (Box 16, Folder 1)
    - Chronological file 1978 (1 of 2) (Box 16, Folder 2)
    - Chronological file 1978 (2 of 2) (Box 16, Folder 3)
    - Chronological file 1979 (1 of 3) (Box 16, Folder 4)
    - Chronological file 1979 (2 of 3) (Box 16, Folder 5)
    - Chronological file 1979 (3 of 3) (Box 16, Folder 6)
    - Chronological file 1980 (1 of 3) (Box 17, Folder 1)
    - Chronological file 1980 (2 of 3) (Box 17, Folder 2)
    - Chronological file 1980 (3 of 3) (Box 17, Folder 3)
    - Chronological file 1981 (1 of 3) (Box 17, Folder 4)
    - Chronological file 1981 (2 of 3) (Box 17, Folder 5)
    - Chronological file 1981 (3 of 3) (Box 17, Folder 6)
    - Chronological file 1982 (1 of 2) (Box 18, Folder 1)
    - Chronological file 1982 (2 of 2) (Box 18, Folder 2)
    - Chronological file 1983 (1 of 2) (Box 18, Folder 3)
    - Chronological file 1983 (2 of 2) (Box 18, Folder 4)
    - Chronological file 1984 (1 of 2) (Box 18, Folder 5)
    - Chronological file 1984 (2 of 2) (Box 18, Folder 6)
    - Chronological file 1985 (1 of 2) (Box 18, Folder 7)
    - Chronological file 1985 (2 of 2) (Box 18, Folder 8)
    - Chronological file 1986 (1 of 3) (Box 19, Folder 1)
    - Chronological file 1986 (2 of 3) (Box 19, Folder 2)
    - Chronological file 1986 (3 of 3) (Box 19, Folder 3)
    - Chronological file 1987 (1 of 2) (Box 19, Folder 4)
    - Chronological file 1987 (2 of 2) (Box 19, Folder 5)
    - Chronological file 1988 (1 of 2) (Box 19, Folder 6)
    - Chronological file 1988 (2 of 2) (Box 19, Folder 7)
    - Chronological file 1989 (1 of 2) (Box 19, Folder 8)
    - Chronological file 1989 (2 of 2) (Box 20, Folder 1)
    - Chronological file 1990 (1 of 2) (Box 20, Folder 2)
    - Chronological file 1990 (2 of 2) (Box 20, Folder 3)
    - Chronological file 1990 (2 of 2) (Box 20, Folder 4)
    - Personal business correspondence, 1973-1976 (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - Professional Writing, 1956-1986
    - Misc Peru (1 of 2), 1956-1982 (Box 20, Folder 6)
    - Misc Peru (2 of 2), 1956-1982 (Box 20, Folder 7)
    - Indonesia - Alternative Strategies for Agricultural Research Support to Transmigration, 1970-1981 (Box 20, Folder 8)
    - Land Tenure and Agricultural Development, 1978 (Box 20, Folder 9)
    - Peru Ministry of Agriculture, 1981 (Box 20, Folder 10)
    - Indira Gandhi, speeches about, 1971 (Box 20, Folder 11)
    - Potential for Cooperative Research and Training between the International Agricultural Research Institute and The Sudan, 1972-1986? (Box 20, Folder 12)
    - IARI Post Graduate School Deemed University Proposal, 1963? (Box 20, Folder 13)
    - International Soil Science Congress Edmonton, Canada, 1978 (Box 20, Folder 14)
    - Farming Systems of the Dry, Semi-arid and Seasonally Dry Climate Regions and Potentials for Their Development, 1978 (Box 20, Folder 15)
  - Research and Related Materials, 1952-1997
    - Farming Systems, 1976-1979 (Box 21, Folder 6)
    - Potential for Cooperative Research and Training between the International Agricultural Research Institute and The Sudan, 1972-1986? (Box 21, Folder 1)
    - Agricultural Research and Research Information in West Africa, 1984 (Box 21, Folder 2)
    - World Bank West Africa Agricultural Research (WAAR) Sahel Sector Bently and Oullette (1 of 3), 1986 (Box 21, Folder 3)
    - World Bank West Africa Agricultural Research (WAAR) Sahel Sector Bently and Oullette (2 of 3), 1986 (Box 21, Folder 4)
    - World Bank West Africa Agricultural Research (WAAR) Sahel Sector by Bently and Oullette (3 of 3), 1986 (Box 21, Folder 5)
    - West Africa Tree Crops Green and Watson, 1986 (Box 21, Folder 6)
    - West Africa Livestock Preliminary on Strategy by R. E. McDowell, 1986 (Box 21, Folder 7)
    - West Africa Research Review Appendices, 1985-1986 (Box 21, Folder 8)
    - CGIAR TAC mission to ILCA, 1979-1981 (Box 21, Folder 9)
    - ILRAD, 1979-1982 (Box 22, Folder 1)
    - India - Agricultural Research Project World Bank (1 of 2), 1975-1978 (Box 22, Folder 2)
    - India - Agricultural Research Project, World Bank (2 of 2), 1975-1978 (Box 22, Folder 3)
    - Indonesia Project Paper Revision for Agricultural Research Project, 1977-1979 (Box 22, Folder 4)
    - International Assistance for Strengthening National Agricultural Research (ISNAR) (1 of 4), 1974-1981 (Box 22, Folder 5)